Seth Climenhaga

Computer Science Student

Profile

I'm a computer science student with a passion for business and software development. I'm experienced in object-oriented programming including design with UML. Currently, I've built applications for web, android, iOS, and desktop platform. In addition to my Computer Science degree, I have a Bachelor of Music during which I took electives in accounting and business.

Portfolio: sethclimenhaga.com

Skills

- C#
- XAML
- Kotlin
- SQL
- HTML & CSS
- WordPress
- Python
- Java
- JavaScript
- React JS
- Visual Studio
- Git & Version Control

Certifications

- Responsive Web Design Certification (Free Code Camp)
- JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures Certification (Free Code Camp)
- Google Suite
- Microsoft Office
- Acadium Training and Apprenticeship (Marketing and Web Design)

Experience

Marketing Assistant: Prospology October 2019 - February 2020

- WordPress (custom HTML & CSS)
- Mail Chimp
- Dubsado

Landscaper: Mike's Landscaping

April 2019 - November 2019

Production: Toyota Motors Manufacturing

June 2018 - April 2019

Projects

ChessGame

ChessGame made in unity for the UWP framework. I implemented and learned about game logic with an object-oriented design, lighting, saving to a binary file. As well as, saving player preferences, and UI in unity. I used Visual Studio for scripting and debugging, and the project was managed with version control.

Tech: Unity, C#, UWP

Link: http://bit.ly/3chessgame

Scales App

The goal of the app is to help a musician with their practice routine by providing selected exercises in a randomized order. Created a multipage app that passes data between activities, saved data in user preferences, and using libraries to hold business logic. Includes the ability to generate custom practice routines based on user inputs.

Tech: Android, Java

Link: http://bit.ly/scales-app

Spotify Mini-Player

Built with the React framework and Electron. This project calls endpoints in the Spotify API and uses the PCKE Authorization flow. The project also implementes a dynamic dropdown menu and makes use of react context.

Tech: React.js, Electron, JavaScript, Axios, JSX

Link: http://bit.ly/spotify-mini

Photography Portfolio

A React Website for a photographer. Includes a sliding gallery using react and jQuery, as well as interactive controls for viewing.

Tech: React.js, JavaScript, JSX **Link**: http://bit.ly/photo-folio

Education

Bachelor of Applied Computer Science

2019-present Sheridan College

Bachelor of Music

2018

Wilfrid Laurier University